<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><edgarSubmission xmlns="http://www.sec.gov/edgar/schedule13D" xmlns:com="http://www.sec.gov/edgar/common">
  <headerData>
    <submissionType>SCHEDULE 13D</submissionType>
    <filerInfo>
      <filer>
        <filerCredentials>
          <cik>0000070858</cik>
          <ccc>XXXXXXXX</ccc>
        </filerCredentials>
      </filer>
      <liveTestFlag>LIVE</liveTestFlag>



    </filerInfo>
  </headerData>
  <formData>
    <coverPageHeader>
      <securitiesClassTitle>VARIABLE RATE DEMAND PREFERRED SHARES</securitiesClassTitle>
      <dateOfEvent>09/17/2025</dateOfEvent>
      <previouslyFiledFlag>false</previouslyFiledFlag>
      <issuerInfo>
        <issuerCIK>0001232860</issuerCIK>
        <issuerCUSIP>09263U205</issuerCUSIP>
        <issuerName>BlackRock Municipal Credit Alpha Portfolio, Inc.</issuerName>
        <address>
          <com:street1>100 BELLEVUE PARKWAY</com:street1>
          <com:city>WILMINGTON</com:city>
          <com:stateOrCountry>DE</com:stateOrCountry>
          <com:zipCode>19809</com:zipCode>
        </address>
      </issuerInfo>
      <authorizedPersons>
        <notificationInfo>
          <personName>Bank of America Corporation</personName>
          <personPhoneNum>980-825-9256</personPhoneNum>
          <personAddress>
            <com:street1>Bank of America Corporate Center</com:street1>
            <com:street2>100 N. Tryon Street</com:street2>
            <com:city>Charlotte</com:city>
            <com:stateOrCountry>NC</com:stateOrCountry>
            <com:zipCode>28255</com:zipCode>
          </personAddress>
        </notificationInfo>
      </authorizedPersons>
    </coverPageHeader>
    <reportingPersons>
      <reportingPersonInfo>
        <reportingPersonCIK>0000070858</reportingPersonCIK>
        <reportingPersonNoCIK>N</reportingPersonNoCIK>
        <reportingPersonName>BANK OF AMERICA CORP /DE/</reportingPersonName>
        <memberOfGroup>b</memberOfGroup>
        <fundType>WC</fundType>
        <legalProceedings>Y</legalProceedings>
        <citizenshipOrOrganization>DE</citizenshipOrOrganization>
        <soleVotingPower>0.00</soleVotingPower>
        <sharedVotingPower>350.00</sharedVotingPower>
        <soleDispositivePower>0.00</soleDispositivePower>
        <sharedDispositivePower>350.00</sharedDispositivePower>
        <aggregateAmountOwned>350.00</aggregateAmountOwned>
        <isAggregateExcludeShares>N</isAggregateExcludeShares>
        <percentOfClass>100.0</percentOfClass>
        <typeOfReportingPerson>HC</typeOfReportingPerson>
      </reportingPersonInfo>
      <reportingPersonInfo>
        <reportingPersonCIK>0001565450</reportingPersonCIK>
        <reportingPersonNoCIK>N</reportingPersonNoCIK>
        <reportingPersonName>Banc of America Preferred Funding Corp</reportingPersonName>
        <memberOfGroup>b</memberOfGroup>
        <fundType>WC</fundType>
        <legalProceedings>N</legalProceedings>
        <citizenshipOrOrganization>DE</citizenshipOrOrganization>
        <soleVotingPower>0.00</soleVotingPower>
        <sharedVotingPower>350.00</sharedVotingPower>
        <soleDispositivePower>0.00</soleDispositivePower>
        <sharedDispositivePower>350.00</sharedDispositivePower>
        <aggregateAmountOwned>350.00</aggregateAmountOwned>
        <isAggregateExcludeShares>N</isAggregateExcludeShares>
        <percentOfClass>100.0</percentOfClass>
        <typeOfReportingPerson>CO</typeOfReportingPerson>
      </reportingPersonInfo>
    </reportingPersons>
    <items1To7>
      <item1>
        <securityTitle>VARIABLE RATE DEMAND PREFERRED SHARES</securityTitle>
        <issuerName>BlackRock Municipal Credit Alpha Portfolio, Inc.</issuerName>
        <issuerPrincipalAddress>
          <com:street1>100 BELLEVUE PARKWAY</com:street1>
          <com:city>WILMINGTON</com:city>
          <com:stateOrCountry>DE</com:stateOrCountry>
          <com:zipCode>19809</com:zipCode>
        </issuerPrincipalAddress>
        <commentText>This Statement on Schedule 13D (this "Statement") relates to the purchase of 350 variable rate demand preferred shares (CUSIP No. 09263U205) ("VRDP Shares") of BlackRock Municipal Credit Alpha Portfolio, Inc. (the "Issuer" or the "Company"). This Statement is being filed by the Reporting Persons (as defined below) as a result of the purchase of VRDP Shares by BAPFC (as defined below). The Issuer's principal executive offices are located at 100 Bellevue Parkway, Wilmington, Delaware 19808.</commentText>
      </item1>
      <item2>
        <filingPersonName>This Statement is being filed on behalf of each of the following persons (collectively, the "Reporting Persons"):
i. Bank of America Corporation ("BAC")
ii. Banc of America Preferred Funding Corporation ("BAPFC")
This Statement relates to the VRDP Shares that were purchased for the account of BAPFC.
</filingPersonName>
        <principalBusinessAddress>The address of the principal business office of BAC is:
Bank of America Corporate Center
100 North Tryon Street
Charlotte, North Carolina 28255
The address of the principal business office of BAPFC is:
214 North Tryon Street
Charlotte, North Carolina 28255
</principalBusinessAddress>
        <principalJob>BAC and its subsidiaries provide diversified global financial services and products.  The principal business of BAPFC is to make investments and provide loans to clients.
Information concerning each executive officer, director and controlling person (the "Listed Persons") of the Reporting Persons is listed on Schedule I attached as an exhibit hereto, and is incorporated by reference herein.  To the knowledge of the Reporting Persons, all of the Listed Persons are citizens of the United States, other than as otherwise specified on Schedule I attached as an exhibit hereto.
</principalJob>
        <hasBeenConvicted>Other than as set forth on Schedule II (attached as an exhibit hereto), during the last five years, none of the Reporting Persons, and to the best knowledge of the Reporting Persons, none of the Listed Persons, have been convicted in a criminal proceeding (excluding traffic violations or similar misdemeanors).</hasBeenConvicted>
        <convictionDescription>Other than as set forth on Schedule II (attached as an exhibit hereto), during the last five years, none of the Reporting Persons, and to the best knowledge of the Reporting Persons, none of the Listed Persons, was a party to a civil proceeding of a judicial or administrative body of competent jurisdiction as a result of which such person was or is subject to a judgment, decree or final order enjoining future violations of, or prohibiting or mandating activities subject to, federal or state securities laws, or finding any violation with respect to such laws.</convictionDescription>
        <citizenship>Citizenship information for Listed Persons provided on Schedule I attached as an exhibit hereto.</citizenship>
      </item2>
      <item3>
        <fundsSource>The aggregate amount of funds used by the Reporting Persons to purchase the securities reported herein was approximately $35,000,000.  The source of funds was the working capital of the Reporting Persons.
The Reporting Persons declare that neither the filing of this Statement nor anything herein shall be construed as an admission that such person is, for the purposes of Section 13(d) of the Exchange Act or any other purpose, (i) acting (or has agreed or is agreeing to act together with any other person) as a partnership, limited partnership, syndicate, or other group for the purpose of acquiring, holding or disposing of securities of the Company or otherwise with respect to the Company or any securities of the Company or (ii) a member of any group with respect to the Company or any securities of the Company
</fundsSource>
      </item3>
      <item4>
        <transactionPurpose>BAPFC has purchased the VRDP Shares for investment purposes. BAPFC acquired the VRDP Shares in a secondary market transaction for a purchase price of $35,000,000.
The Reporting Persons have not acquired the subject securities with any purpose, or with the effect of, changing or influencing control of the issuer, or in connection with or as a participant in any transaction having that purpose or effect.
</transactionPurpose>
      </item4>
      <item5>
        <percentageOfClassSecurities>The responses of the Reporting Persons to Rows (7) through (11) of the cover pages of this Statement are incorporated herein by reference. </percentageOfClassSecurities>
        <numberOfShares>The responses of the Reporting Persons to Rows (7) through (11) of the cover pages of this Statement are incorporated herein by reference.</numberOfShares>
        <transactionDesc>The responses of the Reporting Persons in Item 3 and Item 4 are incorporated herein by reference.  </transactionDesc>
        <listOfShareholders>No other person is known by the Reporting Persons to have the right to receive or the power to direct the receipt of dividends from, or the proceeds from the sale of, VRDP Shares that may be deemed to be beneficially owned by the Reporting Persons.</listOfShareholders>
        <date5PercentOwnership>Not applicable.</date5PercentOwnership>
      </item5>
      <item6>
        <contractDescription>The responses of the Reporting Persons to Item 4 are incorporated herein by reference.  With respect to the VRDP Shares owned by BAPFC, on September 17, 2025, BAPFC assigned certain preferred class voting rights on the VRDP Shares to a voting trust (the "Voting Trust") created pursuant to the Voting Trust Agreement, dated September 17, 2025 among BAPFC, Newport Trust Company, as voting trustee (the "Voting Trustee") and voting consultant (the "Voting Consultant").  Voting and consent rights on the VRDP Shares not assigned to the Voting Trust have been retained by BAPFC.  The Voting Trust provides that with respect to voting or consent matters relating to the voting rights assigned to the Voting Trust, the Voting Consultant analyzes such voting or consent matters and makes a recommendation to the Voting Trustee on voting or consenting.  The Voting Trustee is obligated to follow any such recommendations of the Voting Consultant when providing a vote or consent.
The VRDP Shares will have the benefit of a liquidity purchase obligation at the times and in the manner specified in the VRDP Shares Purchase Agreement, dated as of September 17, 2025, between The Bank of New York Mellon ("BNY") and Bank of America, N.A., as liquidity provider ("BANA"). Certain agreements between the Issuer and BANA as liquidity provider are documented in the VRDP Shares Fee Agreement, dated as of September 17, 2025, between the Issuer and BANA. Certain agreements between the Issuer and BofA Securities, Inc. ("BofA"), as remarketing agent for the VRDP Shares are documented in the VRDP Shares Remarking Agreement, dated as of September 17, 2025, between the Issuer and BofA.
</contractDescription>
      </item6>
      <item7>
        <filedExhibits>Exhibit	Description of Exhibit
99.1	Joint Filing Agreement
99.2	Power of Attorney
99.3	Schedule I
99.4	Schedule II
99.5	Voting Trust Agreement dated September 17, 2025
99.6	VRDP Shares Purchase Agreement, September 17, 2025
99.7	VRDP Shares Fee Agreement, dated September 17, 2025
99.8	VRDP Shares Remarketing Agreement, dated September 17, 2025
</filedExhibits>
      </item7>
    </items1To7>
    <signatureInfo>
      <signaturePerson>
        <signatureReportingPerson>BANK OF AMERICA CORP /DE/</signatureReportingPerson>
        <signatureDetails>
          <signature>/s/ Andres Ortiz</signature>
          <title>Authorized Signatory</title>
          <date>09/24/2025</date>
        </signatureDetails>
      </signaturePerson>
      <signaturePerson>
        <signatureReportingPerson>Banc of America Preferred Funding Corp</signatureReportingPerson>
        <signatureDetails>
          <signature>/s/ Andres Ortiz</signature>
          <title>Authorized Signatory</title>
          <date>09/24/2025</date>
        </signatureDetails>
      </signaturePerson>
    </signatureInfo>
  </formData>

</edgarSubmission>
