<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><!-- Produced by ACII Web Filing Platform, Advanced Computer Innovations, Inc., Copyright (C) 2024-2025 --><edgarSubmission xmlns="http://www.sec.gov/edgar/schedule13D" xmlns:com="http://www.sec.gov/edgar/common">
	<headerData>
		<submissionType>SCHEDULE 13D</submissionType>
		<filerInfo>
			<filer>
				<filerCredentials>
					<cik>0002069079</cik>
					<ccc>XXXXXXXX</ccc>
				</filerCredentials>
			</filer>
			<liveTestFlag>LIVE</liveTestFlag>


		</filerInfo>
	</headerData>
	<formData>
		<coverPageHeader>
			<securitiesClassTitle>Common Stock</securitiesClassTitle>
			<dateOfEvent>09/03/2025</dateOfEvent>
			<issuerInfo>
				<issuerCIK>0001997403</issuerCIK>
				<issuerCUSIP>00098936T</issuerCUSIP>
				<issuerName>ZenaTech, Inc.</issuerName>
				<address>
					<com:street1>777 HORNBY STREET, SUITE 600</com:street1>
					<com:city>VANCOUVER</com:city>
					<com:stateOrCountry>A1</com:stateOrCountry>
					<com:zipCode>V6Z 1S4</com:zipCode>
				</address>
			</issuerInfo>
			<authorizedPersons>
				<notificationInfo>
					<personName>Vin Saini</personName>
					<personPhoneNum>585-510-3890</personPhoneNum>
					<personAddress>
						<com:street1>Advanced Computer Innovations, Inc.</com:street1>
						<com:street2>70 Office Park Way</com:street2>
						<com:city>Pittsford</com:city>
						<com:stateOrCountry>NY</com:stateOrCountry>
						<com:zipCode>14534-1746</com:zipCode>
					</personAddress>
				</notificationInfo>
			</authorizedPersons>
		</coverPageHeader>
		<reportingPersons>
			<reportingPersonInfo>
				<reportingPersonCIK>0002069079</reportingPersonCIK>
				<reportingPersonName>GG Mars Capital, Inc.</reportingPersonName>
				<fundType>PF</fundType>
				<citizenshipOrOrganization>X1</citizenshipOrOrganization>
				<soleVotingPower>1784864</soleVotingPower>
				<sharedVotingPower>0</sharedVotingPower>
				<soleDispositivePower>1784864</soleDispositivePower>
				<sharedDispositivePower>0</sharedDispositivePower>
				<aggregateAmountOwned>1784864</aggregateAmountOwned>
				<percentOfClass>100</percentOfClass>
				<typeOfReportingPerson>CO</typeOfReportingPerson>
			</reportingPersonInfo>
		</reportingPersons>
		<items1To7>
			<item1>
				<securityTitle>Common Stock</securityTitle>
				<issuerName>ZenaTech, Inc.</issuerName>
				<issuerPrincipalAddress>
					<com:street1>777 HORNBY STREET, SUITE 600</com:street1>
					<com:city>VANCOUVER</com:city>
					<com:stateOrCountry>A1</com:stateOrCountry>
					<com:zipCode>V6Z 1S4</com:zipCode>
				</issuerPrincipalAddress>
				<commentText>Item 1 Comment:
This Schedule 13D relates to the common shares of ZenaTech Inc., a British Columbia, Canada corporation (the "Issuer"). The principal executive offices of the Issuer are located at Suite 600, 777 Hornby Street, Vancouver, British Columbia V6Z 1S4 Canada.</commentText>
			</item1>
			<item2>
				<filingPersonName>GG Mars Capital, Inc. (a) This statement on Schedule 13D is filed by GG Mars Capital (the "Reporting Person") subsequent to the exercise of conversion rights under a convertible line of credit provided by the Reporting Person to the Issuer in August 2019.</filingPersonName>
				<principalBusinessAddress>(b) The Reporting Person is organized under the laws of the State of Illinois and its business address is 309 East Rand Road, Arlington Heights, IL 60004</principalBusinessAddress>
				<principalJob>(c) The Reporting Person is in the business of finance.
(d) Information with respect to the directors, officers and controlling shareholders of the Reporting Person is set forth in Schedule A hereto and is incorporated herein by reference. However, the directors and officers of the Reporting Person disclaim beneficial ownership of any shares of the Issuer owned by the Reporting Person.</principalJob>
				<hasBeenConvicted>(d) During the past five years, neither the Reporting Person nor any of its directors or officers has been convicted in a criminal proceeding (excluding traffic violations or similar misdemeanors).</hasBeenConvicted>
				<convictionDescription>(e) During the past five years, neither the Reporting Person nor any of its directors or officers have been a party to a civil proceeding of a judicial or administrative body of competent jurisdiction as a result of which such person was or is subject to a judgment, decree or final order enjoining future violations of, or prohibiting or mandating activities subject to, federal or state securities laws or finding any violation with respect to such laws.</convictionDescription>
				<citizenship>U.S.A.</citizenship>
			</item2>
			<item3>
				<fundsSource>The Reporting Person partially converted amounts outstanding under a line of credit provided by the Reporting Person to the Issuer in August 2019. See Section 5(c) below for more information.</fundsSource>
			</item3>
			<item4>
				<transactionPurpose>The Reporting Persons acquired the Issuer's common stock for investment purposes. None of the Reporting Persons have any plans or proposals which relate to or would result in any of the matters listed in Items 4(a) to 4(j) of Schedule 13D.</transactionPurpose>
			</item4>
			<item5>
				<percentageOfClassSecurities>(a) The Reporting Person holds an aggregate of 1,784,864 common shares of the Issuer, representing approximately 6.694% of the Issuer's outstanding common shares, subsequent to the acquisition of the shares described in Section 5(c) below.</percentageOfClassSecurities>
				<numberOfShares>(b) The Reporting Person has the sole power to vote or to direct the vote and the sole power to dispose or to direct the disposition of the shares.</numberOfShares>
				<transactionDesc>(c) On April 13, 2025, the Reporting Person acquired 430,000 common shares of the Issuer upon the conversion of $753,360 outstanding under a convertible line of credit provided by the Reporting Person to the Issuer in August 2019 at a price of $1.752 per share.</transactionDesc>
				<listOfShareholders>N/A</listOfShareholders>
				<date5PercentOwnership>N/A</date5PercentOwnership>
			</item5>
			<item6>
				<contractDescription>N/A</contractDescription>
			</item6>
			<item7>
				<filedExhibits>A. Information About Directors, Officers and Control Persons of the Reporting Person</filedExhibits>
			</item7>
		</items1To7>
		<signatureInfo>
			<signaturePerson>
				<signatureReportingPerson>GG Mars Capital, Inc.</signatureReportingPerson>
				<signatureDetails>
					<signature>Vivienne Passley</signature>
					<title>President</title>
					<date>09/09/2025</date>
				</signatureDetails>
			</signaturePerson>
		</signatureInfo>
	</formData>

</edgarSubmission>
